http://www.rentlaw.com/rentlaw-com-privacy-notice/

Landlord News
[ 12/24/2019 ]
Charging for Carpet Damage
Carpet
[ 12/24/2019 ]
New York City Housing Authority – 2019 NYC “Worst Landlord”
Habitable
[ 11/25/2019 ]
Landlord-tenant dispute leaves Brooklyn man unconscious
Landlord Tenant Disputes
[ 10/04/2018 ]
NYT Times
– Trumps Sleazy Greedy Landlord
LEGAL
[ 01/17/2018 ]
New Companies in Renters Insurance – Lemonade.com
NEWS
[ 01/02/2018 ]
Introduction to Lead Paint
Lead Paint
Search for:
HomeRentLaw.com Privacy Notice
Scope
This notice provides highlights of the full RentLaw.com Online Privacy Statement. This notice and the full privacy statement apply to those RentLaw.com websites and services that display or link to this notice.
Personal Information
When you register for certain RentLaw.com services, we may ask you to provide personal information.
The information we collect may be combined with information obtained from other RentLaw.com services and other companies.
We may use cookies and other technologies to keep track of your interactions with our sites and services to offer a personalized experience. This includes advertisements displayed on our site.
We Do Not Sell or Share this information with any 3rd Party.
Email and Other Services – Your Choice
You can stop the delivery of promotional e-mail from a RentLaw.com site or service by following the instructions in the e-mail you receive.
Uses of Personal Information
We use the information we collect to provide the services you request. Our services may include the display of personalized content and advertising.
We may use your information to inform you of other products or services offered by RentLaw.com and its affiliates, and to send you relevant survey invitations related to RentLaw.com services.
We do not sell, rent, or lease our customer lists to third parties. A promotion may be delivered by RentLaw.com which you may opt out of when you join RentLaw.com
E-mail Newsletters
If users wish to subscribe to our e-mail newsletters, we ask for contact information (such as name, e-mail address, phone number) and information about the subscriber’s professional interests and responsibilities. Recipients of our newsletters can unsubscribe using the instructions listed at the end of the e-mail newsletter.
Contact RentLaw.com
For more information about our privacy practices write us.
RentLaw.com
Privacy Control
6 Cypress Ave
Oakhurst, NJ 07755
NOTIFICATION and CHANGES
If we change our Privacy Statement, we will post those changes on this page so our users are aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under which circumstances, if any, we disclose it. Users should check this policy frequently to keep abreast of any changes.
– Tenant Screening –
LOGIN or SIGN UP to Start Screening Now
Our Tenant Screening FAQs
Top Stops on RentLaw.com
Request Security Deposit Return
Breaking a Lease
Tenant Screening Guide
FORMS
